BRANNON LEE

Los Angeles, CA 90291 · (650) 773 - 7229

brannon.r.lee@gmail.com · brannonlee.netlify.app · linkedin.com/in/brannon-lee/

Entry-level web developer with practical experience in website development, and fifteen years experience in client relations looking to use my training in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to develop engaging and user-focused web experiences that clearly communicate through digital content.

SKILLS

- Coding: HTML5, CSS3,
- Programming: JavaScript, jQuery, React; Familiarity with TypeScript and NextJs
- Software: Adobe Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Google Gimp, Spark; Microsoft Word, Access, Excel, and PowerPoint; Pro Tools; Logic Pro;
- Proven ability to communicate, coordinate, problem solve, work through obstacles, and manage uncontrollable sudden changes
- Adept in writing or analyzing contracts and client briefs
- Customer service

EXPERIENCE

APRIL 2004 - MAY 2020

DESTINATION MANAGER / EVENT COORDINATOR, PACIFIC ROAD USA

- Web design and maintenance
- Database creation & maintenance (MS Access/Excel)
- Design and management of custom educational experiences for international students including:
 - Curriculum design & development; coordination of instructors & interpreters; management of logistics, materials, budget, and emergency preparedness; domestic and international communication & coordination between hotels, group leaders, schools, and location representatives.

JANUARY 2018 - PRESENT

FREELANCE WEBSITE DESIGN & MAINTENANCE, BRANNON ROLLER LEE

- Freelance web design and maintenance for local artists including:
 - Page layout and UI/UX design
 - HTML/CSS and responsive design
 - JavaScript and JQuery for responsive menu, interactive features, and a dynamic user experience
 - Clients have included: Calahan (2017 present) www.calahanmusic.com, RokToy (2018 - present) – www.roktoy.com (using Wix), Drunk in the Garage (2017) – www.drunkinthegarage.com

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE – WEBSITE SOFTWARE SPECIALIST – SANTA MONICA COLLEGE (DEC 2019) B.A. - FILM/TV/RADIO (MINOR IN BUSINESS) - SAN JOSE STATE UNIVERSITY